Guide to the Northup & O'Brien Architectural Records
Northup & O'Brien Architectural Records
- Specifications, 31 linear feet
  - Library Building (H & P), Salem College, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - George H. Bernhardt, Administration Building (H & P), undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Mr. and Mrs. J. E. Johnson Residence (P & H), undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Gardener's Cottage, Mr. W. M. Reynolds, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Winston-Salem First Presbyterian Church Management (H & P), undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Nurses Home, NC Baptist Hospital, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Sterilizer Equipment, City Colored Hospital, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Kitchen Equipment, City Colored Hospital, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Nurses Home (H & P), City Colored Hospital, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Sedge Garden School, Forsyth County, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - J. L. Hedrick Hotel Building, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - State Office Building, Raleigh, N.C., undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    This project is probably the State of North Carolina Education Building (1937).
  - City Hall, Albermale, N.C., undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Dormitory Building, Winston-Salem Teacher's College, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Auditorium and Dining Hall, Winston-Salem Teacher's College, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Auditorium and Dining Hall, Winston-Salem Teacher's College, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Storefront, W. N. Reynolds (No Specs), undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - R. E. Lasater, Building, Job Specs., undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Winston-Salem Airport Terminal Building, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Office Building and Sve. Stn., Quality Oil Company, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - First Federal S & L, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Domestic Science Building, Stokes Co. Schools, King, N.C., undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Auditorium Addition, Pinnacle School, Pinnacle, N.C., undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - South Junior High School, Winston-Salem, N.C., undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - South Junior High School, Winston-Salem, N.C., undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Addition to Pire Hall School, Stokes Co., N.C. (No Specs), undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Altercations and Additions to Francisco School Building, Francisco, N.C., undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Mineral Springs School, Altercations and Additions, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Boiler Room Equipment, Mr. M. E. Motsinger, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - R.C. Vaughn (No spec)/Medical Center (No spec), undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Anchor Store Building, Winston-Salem, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - S. B. Coley Residence, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Mrs. T. W. Watson, Residence, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Infirmary Building, Greensboro College, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Cotton Warehouse, State of N.C., undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Cotton Warehouse, State of N.C., undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Colored Ward Building, Forsyth County Tubercular Hospital, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Colored Ward Building, Forsyth County Tubercular Hospital, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - D. L. Cozart Residence, Raleigh, N.C., undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Emory James Apartment House, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Library and Administration Building, Winston-Salem Teachers College, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Library and Administration Building, Winston-Salem Teachers College, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Driveways and Walks, Winston-Salem Teachers College, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Science Building, Winston-Salem Teachers College, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Science Building, Winston-Salem Teachers College, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Department of Justice Building, State of N.C., undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Department of Justice Building, State of N.C., undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Department of Justice Building, State of N.C., undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - No specs., undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Office Building, Salem Steel Company, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Danbury Courthouse Stokes Co., undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Mr. T. Henry Wilson Residence, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Gymnasium, Rural Hall, N.C., undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Quay Blaylock, Heating, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - T. O. Moore, Residence, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Gordon Gray Residence, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - No specs., undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - R. J. Reynolds Residence, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - W. A. Goodson Residence, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Cooleemee School Addition, Davie County, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - First National Bank, Winston-Salem (no specs), undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Mr. Pat Cummings Residence, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Mr. and Mrs. J. G. Goldston Residence and Garage, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Old Richmond Gym (no spec)/Alteration - C.T. Leinbach(no spec), undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Mr. John S. Creech Residence, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - S. B. Coley Residence, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - P.H. Hanes Store (no spec), 10-11-39 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - J. C. B. Ehringhaus Residence, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - A. B. Henley Residence, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Old Town Gym (no spec)/Phil School Add.(no spec), undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - George H. Bernhardt Residence, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Refreshment Stand (no spec), undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Earl N. Phillips Residence, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Add: To Mineral Springs School (no spec)/Alt: To Kernersville School (no spec), undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - C. W. Long Residence, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - City National Bank, Winston-Salem, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Kate Bitting Reynolds Memorial Hospital - Altercations and Additions, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Boiler Plant Equipment, City Memorial Hospital, Winston-Salem, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - N.C. Baptist Hospital, Altercations and Additions, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Bowman Gray School of Medicine, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Boiler Room Equipment, City Market, Winston-Salem, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Negro Comm. Building (no spec), undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - H. L. Residence, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Plumbing and Heating Refectory, Salem College, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Girl's Dormitory, The Children's Home, Winston-Salem, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Double House, Children's Home, Winston-Salem, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Home Moravian Church, Winston-Salem, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Office Building, Durham Life Insurance Company, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Plumbing and Heating, Durham Life Insurance Company, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Additions, Durham Life Insurance Company, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Elevator, Durham Life Insurance Company, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - S & W Cafeteria Durham Life Ins. Co., undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Forsyth Country Club, Alterations and Additions, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Mess Hall, Camp Lasater, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Thomas Barber, Residence, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Charles L. Kearnes, Residence, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Forsyth Country Club, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Home Economics Cottage, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Jackson Park School, Rowan County, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Grayson Pleasants, Residence, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Office Building, Winston Printing Company, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Enochville School, Rowan County, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Woodrow Wilson School, Addition to Auditorium, Rowan County, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Landis Vocational School, Rowan County, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Colored Grade School, Salisbury, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Amos Hosiery Mill, High School, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - C. E. Elberson Residence, Alteration and Addition to Boiler Room, Residence, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Dormitory Building, Salem College, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - John Coan, Residence, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - R. B. Terry, Residence, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Bowman Gray Institute of Medical Research, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Gordan Gray, W41 MM Transmitter Building, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Revenue Building, Altercations and Additions, Raleigh, N.C., undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Housing Authority of Winston-Salem (no spec), undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - WSJS Transmitter Building, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Altercations to Babcock Residence, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Nurses Home - Altercation and Addition, N.C. Baptist Hospital, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Nurses Home - Altercation and Addition, N.C. State Hospital, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Morrison Training School, Hoffman, N.C., undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Alterations and Additions, N.C. State Hospital, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Thos. Wilson, Residence, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Luncheonette Building, Woman's College, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - E. D. Lingle, Bakery Building, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Charles L. Kerns, Residence, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Agricultural Labortory, NCSU, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - William M. Butler, Residence, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Winston-Salem Leaf Tobacco Building, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Medical Building, Drs. Malloy and Jordan, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Dormitories "D" and "E", NCSU, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Dormitories "D" and "E", NCSU, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Play Room Addition (no spec)/Henly Paper Co. (no spec), undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Epileptic Buildings, Altercations, NC State Hospital, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - B. F. Huntley Additions, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Horticulture Labarotry, NCSU, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Triangle Business Center, Service Station, Store, and Office; Clemmons Enterprise, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Waughton Baptist Church, Wintson-Salem, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Mount Tabor Methodist Church, Heating Equipment, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Washington Mills, School Building, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Mix Blending Plant, Krispy Kreme Doughnut Company, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Lewisville School, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Lewisville School Additions, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Leazar Dining Hall, NCSU, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Homemaking Cottage, UNC-G, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Mineral Springs Elementary No. 1, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Laundry Building, Women's College of UNC, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Armory, NCSU, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Badin School Gym, Stanly County, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Endy School Building, Stanly County, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Locust School Building, Stanly County, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Cafeteria, NCSU, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Ridgecrest School Gym, Stanly County, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Millingport School Gym, Stanly County, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Aquadale School Gym, Stanly County, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Dining Hall - Addition and Alteration, Woman's College, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Piedmont Federal and L. Association Building, Winston-Salem, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Altercation and Addition - Atkins Hall, Winston-Salem Teacher's College, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Altercation and Addition to Cottages, Stonewall Jackson Training School, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Library, Woman's College, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Broughton Building Renovation, N.C. State Hospital (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Building for Epleptic Children, N.C. State Hospital, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Clark Building Renovation, N.C. State Hospital, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - General Engineering Laboratory Building, NCSU, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - General Engineering Laboratory Building, Plumbing and Heating, NCSU, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Laundry and Service Building, ASU, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Addition to School Building, Children's Home, Winston-Salem, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Dormitory - UNCG, General, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Dormitory - Heating and Plumbing, UNC-G, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Headhouse for Greenhouses, NCSU, General and Electric, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - UNC - Hospital, General and Electric, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - UNC - Hospital, General and Electric, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - UNC - Hospital, General and Electric, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - UNC - Hospital, General, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - UNC - Hospital; Plumbing, Heating, Ventilation, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - UNC - Hospital; Elevators, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - UNC - Hospital; Water Saving Equipment, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - UNC Hospital - Change Orders, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - UNC Hospital - Change Orders, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Nurses Home Additions; Kate Bitting Reynolds Memorial Hospital, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Home Economics Building, UNC-G, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Home Economics Building - Plumbing and Heating, UNC-G, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Home Economics Building, Change Orders, UNC-G, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Agronomy Building - General Specs., NCSU, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Agronomy Building - Change Orders, NCSU, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Building for Disturbed Men, NC State Hospital, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Building for Disturbed Men, NC State Hospital, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Building for Disturbed Men, NC State Hospital, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Mechanical Engineering Building, NCSU, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Mechanical Engineering Building, NCSU, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Mechanical Engineering Lab, NCSU, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Music and Art Building, ASU, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Music and Art Building, ASU, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Music and Art Building, ASU, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Education Building Addition; Raleigh - State of N.C., undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Addition to Education Building; State of N.C., undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Student Union Building - Woman's College; General Specs., undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Student Union Building - Woman's College, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Student Union Building - Woman's College; Change Orders, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Salem College; Science Building - General, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Salem College; Science Building - Plumbing, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Salem College; Science Building - Heating, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Salem College; Science Building - Change Orders, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - ASU - Girls' Dorm - General and Electrical, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - ASU - Girls' Dorm - Plumbing and Heating, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - UNC Medical Building, Steam Line - General and Electrical, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - UNC - Nurses Home - General, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - UNC - Nurses Home - Mechanical, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - UNC School of Nursing - Change Orders, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Children's Home Dorm; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - ASU - Boys' Dorm - General and Electrical, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - ASU - Boys' Dorm - Heating, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - ASU - Boys' Dorm - Change Orders, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Mineral Springs School #2 - Altercations and Additions; General, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Mineral Springs School #2 - Altercations and Additions; Plumbing, Heating, and Electrical, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Mineral Springs School #2 - Altercations and Additions; Change Orders, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Happy Hill Gardens; Winston-Salem Housing Authority, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Happy Hill Gardens; Winston-Salem Housing Authority, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Winston-Salem Teacher's College; Boys Dorm - General, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Winston-Salem Teacher's College; Boys Dorm - Change Orders, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - NCSU Engineering Buildings; Altercations and Additions - General, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - NCSU Engineering Buildings; Altercations and Additions - Plumbing, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - NCSU Engineering Buildings; Altercations and Additions, undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - UNCG - Infirmary; General, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - UNCG - Infirmary; Mechanical, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - UNC - Medical School Addition, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - UNC - Medical School Addition, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Reynolds High School; Gymnasium, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Reynolds High School; Gymnasium - change orders, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Winston-Salem Teachers' College; Infirmary Building - General, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Winston-Salem Teachers' College; Infirmary Building - Change Orders, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - NCSU; D. H. Hill Library - General, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - NCSU; D. H. Hill Library - Change Orders, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Happy Hill Gardens; Winston-Salem Housing Authority, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Atkins High School; Gymnasium-General, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Atkins High Gymnasium - Change Orders, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - UNC; Dental School - General, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - UNC; Dental School - Change Orders, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - UNC; Infirmary Building - General, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - UNC; Infirmary Building - Change Orders, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Winston-Salem Teacher's College; Girls Dorm - General, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Physical Education Building; Winston-Salem Teacher's College, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Piedmont Park; Winston-Salem Teacher's College, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Piedmont Park; Winston-Salem Teacher's College - Revisions to Water Dist. System, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Textbook and Archives Building - General; Raleigh, N.C., undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Remodeling Vocational Building - General; Winston-Salem Teacher's College, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - UNC; Medical School Building - Sounth Wing Addition - General, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - UNC; Hospital Water Main Ext., undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Winston-Salem Public Library - General, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Kimberly Park Terrace; Winston-Salem Housing Authority- General, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Kimberly Park Terrace; Winston-Salem Housing Authority- Landscape, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Shop and Maintenance Building; Woman's College, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Transformer Equipment; Woman's College, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Forsyth County Agricultural Building - General, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Winston-Salem Teacher's College; Electrical Renovation, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Marine Corps Air Station - Renovation of Building 137; Cherry Point, N.C., undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Nursery School; Woman's College, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Crane Equipment; Marine Corps Air Station; Cherry Point, N.C., undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Bowman Gray School of Medicine - Transformer, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Millingport School - Cafeteria and Class Room Addition Stanly County, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Air Intercept Training Facility; Marine Corps Air Station; Cherry Point, N.C., undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Gary Ct. Apartments - Parking, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Mess Hall and Galley Rehab; USMC Auxiliary Landing Strip; Wilmington, N.C., undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Carolina Hall; Winston-Salem Teachers College, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Krispy Kreme; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Home Builders Association; Albermarle, N.C., undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Buena Vista School; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - W. A. Whitaker School - Class Room Addition; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Amos Hosiery Mill Addition; High Point, undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - East Winston Branch Library, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Dental School Addition, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Hangar Relocation; Marine Corps Aux. Landing Strip; Wilmington, N.C., undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Library Altercations and Additions; ASU, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Library Altercations and Additions - Change Orders; ASU, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Cleveland Ave. Homes; Winston-Salem Housing Authority, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Cleveland Ave. Homes - Landscape; Winston-Salem Housing Authority, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Davie County Office Building, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Woodland School - Addition; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Parkign Garage and Stores; Frazier Company; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - White Rock School, Forsyth County, N.C., undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Ardmore School Addition, Winston-Salem, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Ardmore School Addition - Change Orders; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Downtown Garage Addition; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - New North School; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - New North School - Change Orders; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Site Improvements; Winston-Salem Teacher's College, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Tryon Palace Restoration - Mechanical, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Anchor County Parking Deck; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Granville School Auditorium; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Power Plant and Shop Building; Winston-Salem Teacher's College, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Power Plant and Shop Bldg.; Winston-Salem Teachers College, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Cafeteria and Shop; Reynolds High School, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Cafeteria and Shop; Reynolds High School Winston-Salem, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Happy Hill Gardens; Winston-Salem Housing Authority, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Happy Hill Gardens Landscape, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Elevator; Forsyth Co. Courthouse, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Nursing School Add.; Winston-Salem Teacher's College, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Marine Corps Reserve Addition; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Parking Deck; Reynolds Realty, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Power Plant and Laundry; Salem College - General and Change Orders, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Air Conditioning; Forsyth Co. Courthouse, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Air Conditioning; City Hall--Winston-Salem, undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Tom Cash School; Forsyth County, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Academy Annex; Salem College, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Academy Annex; Salem College-Change Orders, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal Church; Education Bldg., undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal Church; Education Bldg., undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Jerico Motel; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Marine Corps Air Station; Flight Test and Emergency Repair Facility, undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Smoke House Alt. - Thruway Shopping Center; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Research Lab. Addition; R. J. Reynolds Tobacco Company, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Research Lab Addition.- Change Orders; R. J. Reynolds Tobacco Company, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Research Lab Addition; R. J. Reynolds Tobacco Company, undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Kimberly High School; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Kimberly High School; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Mary Reynolds Babcock Dorm; Salem College, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Konnoak Hills Elementary; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Konnoak Hills Elementary; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Columbia Heights; High School, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Columbia Heights; High School, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Classroom Building; Winston-Salem College, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)